Hi, and welcome to the first lesson of this course,
Introduction to the machinery workflow.
Together, we will take the step necessary for any machine learning project,
from the problem setup to the model-building phase,
and the error analysis.
This lesson will focus on the high-level component of any machine learning workflow,
and we will dive into the details later in the course.
First of all, what is machine learning?
A machine learning algorithm is a type of artificial intelligence or AI,
where a computer is learning how to extract information from data.
To train a machine learning algorithm,
we have to fit it with example data.
In this course, we'll be using a few different data-set.
But for now, we will focus on
the German traffic sign recognition benchmark or GTSRB data-set.
This data-set consists of thousands of
images of traffic sign with their associated labels.
We will focus on classifying these traffic signs
using different algorithm in the following lessons.
In this lesson, we'll use it as an example of a task you could
face in your future job as a machine learning engineer. Let's get started.